最后一个问题
Final question, girl.
特利斯坦劈开宇宙太虚的时候
When Tristan split the galactic pangaea,
他跟那里的原住民说了什么
what did he say to the scattering colonies?
狼人们  迁居他星吧
"Run to the stars, wolves.
但是永远以你们的家人为重
But always put first your families.
因为  正是他们的爱
For their love
你们才会出现在宇宙
keeps you tethered to the universe."
哇  你还必须得承认
Wow. You've gotta admit...
玛蒂真心保住了丽芙的面子啊
Maddie's making Liv look really good.
她骗不了任何人
She's not fooling anyone.
却骗了这里的所有人
Well, except everyone here.
哇  丽芙鲁尼
Well, Liv Rooney...
你通过了
I'm sold.
我是说  你演特利斯坦会很棒的
I mean, you will make a great Tristan Lycanth.
向特利斯坦小姐致礼
All hail the she-Tristan!
呃  知会一声
And, FYI...
我舞会还没邀请别人
I currently am available for le prom.
但是好像你
But your window of opportunity
没有机会啦
is closing.
邦
Boop!
亚迪
Artie.
你好好想想
Are you serious?
你真能接受我姐姐出演崔特利斯坦吗
You can accept my sister playing Tristan?
你还有什么
What part of...
想不通的  哈
Don't you understand?
这么说  帕克和我是最后
Okay, so Parker and I are the only ones
持干戈之矛的人咯
that have a problem with this?
呃  话说回来
Um, speak for yourself.
丽芙也得我心
She won me over too.
亚迪  给我来条尾巴
Artie, tail me.
直到此刻  我才意识到
It was at that moment that I realized
我才是可能会伤害丽芙的
I was the crazy fanboy
那个脑残粉
that I was trying to protect Liv from.
我才是被家族逐弃的人
I was untethered from my family.
我才是离群之狼
I was the lone wolf.
并且  我不该吃那 15 个泡泡眼球糖的
And I should not have eaten 15 gummy eyeballs.
亚迪
You know what, Artie...
我也要一条尾巴
tail me too.
向特利斯坦小姐致礼
All hail the she-Tristan!